Where do you think you're going?
You've got no place to go.
Don't hide like a sneaky little rat.
Show yourself.
You should have gotten on that plane.
You will regret your decision.
I'm going to find you.
No matter what it takes.
Where to, sir?
To Seoul, please.
All right.
I'm sorry, but…
could you give me five minutes?
Jun-ho.
Jun-ho, can you hear me?
Doctor! I need a doctor in here!
My son just opened his eyes!
In-ho.
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 1
BREAD AND LOTTERY
2 YEARS LATER
What the hell?
You're not wearing a helmet.
Your license, please.
Damn it. Isn't this entrapment?
Hiding to catch people is shady.
You want to squeeze money
out of broke citizens?
Your license, please.
Hold on.
Look, can't you just let us go?
I'm wearing one.
No, ma'am.
Hey, you're really hot.
I could charge you with obstruction.
You're a tough cookie.
Come on, get in here.
Damn, great picture.
The fine for not wearing a helmet
is 20,000 won. Pay it on time.
Hey, can I post this picture online?
Are you on Instagram?
Let's follow each other!
Where are you going?
Hey! Where are you going? What about me?
You can ask that stupid pig
for a ride in his patrol car!
Hey!
You asshole!
Damn it!
Hwang Jun-ho!
Is this why you transferred here?
To be called a "stupid pig"?
Chief.
Do you like vinegar on these?
It's been so long, I can't quite remember.
Jun-ho, stop wasting your time out here.
Come back to the Major Crimes Division.
Wait, not on the onions.
Just on the pickled radish, right?
For God's sake, are you still brooding?
Look, I've tried.
I've made enough appeals
to the authorities,
and I had the coast guard
search the area for days.
I know. Just eat your noodles
before they get soggy.
Listen.
I want to believe you.
No, I do believe you.
But we never got those photos
you said you sent.
Your phone is at the bottom of the sea,
and you don't know where that island is.
Those games you said you saw,
where people got killed?
I've tried to make
the higher-ups believe it,
but there's just not enough evidence.
The only evidence is
the untraceable bullet in your shoulder.
And let me remind you, smart-ass.
You went rogue with a gun
and suddenly turned up at death's door.
I haven't told you this before,
but when you woke up,
they were ready to fire you,
and I went out of my way to stop them.
Right, thank you.
I'll be forever indebted to you, sir.
You sarcastic little shit.
Look, we're the police.
Firemen fight fire with water,
and the police--
"Fight crime with evidence."
I know. That's why I work in traffic now.
You see,
we always have clear evidence here.
Running red lights,
speeding, not wearing a helmet…
Our evidence is there in pictures.
No one can dispute it.
Jun-ho, do you really not remember
who shot you?
No.
In-ho.
Come with me.
In-ho, why…
Where are we going?
Look, there's a motel here.
Here?
What?
Excuse me.
Is anyone there?
Are you open or what?
Hello?
Babe, do we have to stay here?
Looks like a dump.
The lights are off too. Are they closed?
Good. No lights means the rooms are full.
Let's go someplace else.
How do you know that?
Who told you?
Do you have to ask? I just know.
You just know?
What are you, a motel expert?
Seriously? You're a dick.
-"A dick"…
-You said you liked how I knew everything.
Just tell me how you knew.
Did your ex-boyfriend tell you?
Get lost!
Why can't you answer me?
Who's there?
Player 456.
Looking for these?
It's me.
I got you some food and medicine.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Come on, you don't look any better.
I told you not to overdo it, didn't I?
You'll burn yourself out
before you find that guy.
How did it go?
We checked all the subway stations
on Lines 1 to 4 today.
But again, nothing.
Time of search?
From 10 a.m. to 10 p.m.
We took one-hour lunch and dinner breaks.
We take turns eating.
What if he knows you're onto him
and he's gone somewhere else?
We've been searching for two years
but found no trace of him.
Tomorrow, get more men, extend the search.
From the first train to the last.
Check all the lines at the same time.
All the lines at the same time?
Pulling off something that extensive
would mean shelling out
a ton of money on staff.
I was approached by him three years ago,
around this time of year.
If the game is still going on,
he's recruiting players right now.
It may take another year
if we don't find him now.
Yeah… Okay, I got it.
I… I'll make sure to find him this time.
I promise.
-Woo-seok.
-Yeah.
From tomorrow,
we're going to need more people.
What? But how many more?
Just call everyone you know.
-But--
-Also, we start at 6 a.m.
So don't stay out drinking.
Go home and get some sleep.
At 6 a.m.? Who'd play ddakji at--
Come on. Boss. I've thought about it,
but it just doesn't make any sense--
No. I'm sure something is going on.
As you know, most of the people
who owe me money
have disappeared over the last few years.
-I never got any money back…
-Okay.
So you think everyone who owes you money
was taken to some island
and got killed playing kiddie games.
That sounds--
Goddamnit, I barely believe a word,
but I'm doing this for the money!
If Seong Gi-hun hadn't come to me himself
to pay off his debt
and hired me for this job,
I couldn't have paid you all
or kept the business running.
I know that, but--
Then shut up and search
with your eyes wide open.
Okay.
If we find that bastard with the ddakji,
we will get a one-billion won reward.
One billion?
That's right.
Do you want to believe his story now?
-But--
-Tell you what.
Whoever finds the guy,
I'll give you half the money. Okay?
-So 500 million?
-That's right!
Well, what are we waiting for?
Five hundred million won!
Captain.
Hello.
How have you been?
Same old, same old.
When the weather is good, I catch fish.
When it's bad, I catch a buzz.
You still look great for someone
who drinks every day, Captain Park.
Save it and put this on.
We've got a mystery island to find.
Where can I take you today, Captain Hwang?
We've checked pretty much everywhere
over the past year and a half,
but you want to keep going,
and I don't know where else to take you.
Where are you, mystery island?
Some places couldn't be checked properly
because of the conditions or tide changes.
I've narrowed them down.
Let's try here today.
Sure thing, Captain Hwang.
Man, why did I have to save a drowning man
and put myself through all this trouble?
I pity myself.
SUNSHINE CAPITAL
All right. Listen up.
The person we're looking for
is this guy.
He's tall, probably over 6 ft.
He's a good-looking fella in a nice suit,
with a briefcase in hand.
And in that briefcase,
he's got stacks of money and ddakji.
He plays ddakji with strangers
at subway stations, and afterwards…
he gives them a card like this.
-I can't see.
-What does it say?
The moment you spot someone like that,
call the number we gave you.
Take a picture.
-Hold on, I can't see.
-Move your head.
-Please move!
-Just a little bit!
All right. Are you done?
Here are your designated areas.
Group 1, Lines 1 and 2.
Group 2, Lines 3 and 4.
Group 3, Lines 5 and 6.
Group 4, Lines 7 and 8. And Group 5,
the Gyeongui-Jungang Line
and the Airport Railroad.
From the first train to the last,
search the stations one by one.
Every single one of them.
Do not skip a single station.
-Yes, sir!
Now, after searching each station,
take a picture to prove it
and send it to the group chat.
Otherwise, you won't get paid.
Are we clear?
-Yes, sir!
-One last thing.
The team that finds the guy
gets a bonus of 500 million won.
Damn, 500 million? Really?
After you, sir.
Let's go make 500 million won!
We're heading to the subway stations.
I'll be on standby at the usual spot.
Keep me posted.
Okay.
SEARCHING YONGDU STATION
SEARCHING OKSU STATION
Have you seen a guy like this?
He's tall and…
-A man in a suit, with a briefcase.
-I'm not sure.
If he flips mine like this,
it means I lose, right?
So I get slapped.
Like this. Have you seen it?
A man in a suit
slapping people in the face.
-Excuse me.
-Who are you?
Sorry.
Excuse me. Let me take a quick look.
Hey, it's all right.
Just a quick check.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
It'll be quick.
How did it go?
Right here.
Smile.
-One.
-Look serious.
HANGANGJIN STATION CLEAR
-We need a photo.
-Yeah.
TODAY'S SEARCH HAS ENDED
Captain Hwang, we're heading back now.
Yeah.
We've got to eat something first.
Hold on tight!
For God's sake.
Time for another selfie.
Let's take one now.
Oh, man.
TODAY'S SEARCH HAS ENDED
I told you this was a terrible idea
in this weather.
There are whirlpools in that area.
No one ever really goes there,
not even the big boats.
We're lucky we didn't capsize.
We almost joined the mermaids
looking for that island.
I'm sorry.
Why did I have to pull you
out of the water that day
and end up risking my life
doing this shit for nothing?
I'm forever grateful.
Do you know how many islands there are
within a 6-mile radius
of where I found you?
There are hundreds.
And the currents are strong out there.
There's no telling how far
you drifted with that buoy.
You can't even remember which island
you fell from,
let alone the island
where they play the games.
So how in the world would we find it?
You're right. It's time to stop.
We've done enough.
You say that now,
but I know you'll be back next week.
Thank you for saving my life
and helping me look for the island.
I promise I'll find a way to repay you.
You don't have to do that.
I'm sad to hear that
you won't be coming back.
I'll come visit from time to time.
All right.
Come and catch squid with me, okay?
It's so hard to find good crew members
these days.
I'll pay you more than
what you make as an officer.
Oh, how much?
Well, let's talk about that over a drink
when we get back.
There's the port.
The doors are opening.
The doors are closing.
There.
You've got to be kidding me with this.
Even construction workers
get proper food these days.
This is just… Damn.
You little…
You're making easy money down here
in the middle of summer.
Count your blessings.
You idiot.
Go work at a construction site then.
Seriously though.
How much of Seong Gi-hun's story
do you actually believe?
We've been searching every subway station
in the city all summer,
but no one's ever seen the guy.
Here's the thing.
-I've been thinking.
-Yeah?
Seong Gi-hun may be crazy,
but he wouldn't waste billions
looking for someone who doesn't exist.
He's onto something for sure.
Come on, boss. We've been searching
these stations for the past two years.
Not days, years. Two whole years.
My wife says I should find that bastard,
get myself into the game,
and bring home 45.6 billion won.
If someone were playing ddakji down here,
we would've found him--
Yes!
Hello?
We've found the guy. It's him.
Are you sure?
The ddakji, slapping, and money.
It's just like you said.
He's handing over the card now.
Where are you?
Jonggak Station, but he's leaving.
I'm on my way.
Follow him carefully,
and keep me updated on his location.
Stay on him until I get there.
I got it. I'll be in touch.
JUN-HEE
OBSTETRICS AND GYNECOLOGY
The phone is off.
You will be directed to voicemail…
Ms. Kim Jun-hee.
Is there a Ms. Kim Jun-hee here?
Ms. Park Mi-yeong.
-Yes.
We're ready for you.
All of them?
I'm sorry? A hundred scratchers?
Good dreams last night?
Hey. He's gone into Tapgol Park.
I'm heading there now.
Do not approach him. Wait for me.
Okay. Hurry up.
Excuse me, sir.
Hello.
You seem to be struggling,
living a life with no future.
I have a little gift for you today.
A gift?
What is it?
You can only have one.
Bread, or lottery. You have to choose one.
SORRY!
You lost.
The coin, please.
-Woo-seok.
-Yeah.
What the hell do you think he's doing?
I don't know.
Maybe he's a good guy. I'm confused.
SORRY!
Damn it.
Damn it! Fucking hell.
How come he's not giving us one?
Beats me.
Man, I had a lucky dream last night.
What is he doing?
Why would you throw away
perfectly good food like that?
I gave you a chance,
and you made your choice.
I'm not the one who threw these away.
It was you, ladies and gentlemen.
What's wrong with him?
Plate number 2071, pull over.
Plate number 2071, pull over now.
You take this one.
Me?
They'll either beg you to let it slide
or complain about us hiding
to give people tickets.
Don't be unkind,
but don't listen to them go on about it.
Just be polite and professional. Got it?
Yes, sir.
Sir, you were going over the speed limit.
Can I see your license?
Taxi!
Come on!
Please follow that orange cab over there.
-What?
-Shit.
I'll pay double if you catch up with it.
All right!
Where are you? Are you coming?
I'll be there soon.
This guy is a total nutcase.
He's in a cab now.
I'll keep you updated, but hurry!
I got it.
The fine for speeding is 60,000 won.
Make sure--
That was quick.
Did you do everything right?
Well, he just took the ticket
and drove off without saying anything.
That's suspicious. Did you run his ID?
Nothing came up.
I don't know what he does,
but he had a lot of cell phones
and tablets in his car.
SEONG GI-HUN
NO CRIMINAL RECORD FOUND
-Turn right here.
-All right.
Boss, he's getting out!
He just got out.
I'll send the address.
Call when you arrive.
You can drop us off here.
Okay.
Here. Thank you.
Where's Seong?
He'll be here in ten minutes.
Hey, we might lose him if we wait.
Let's just get him by ourselves.
-By ourselves?
-That's right. Are you scared?
It's two against one.
Don't be a coward now you're married.
It's just that
something seems off with that guy.
Besides, Seong told us
to wait until he gets here.
But what if we lose him?
What if Seong doesn't give us the money?
Woo-seok. It's a billion won!
You'll give me half, right?
Don't you trust me?
I officiated your wedding, for God's sake.
Come on.
-Hey, you! Stop!
-Stop!
Hey, you!
Boss!
Come on! Come at me, damn it!
Woo-seok…
SEONG GI-HUN
Mr. Seong.
Please help me.
I need to find my brother.
I'm sorry.
I'm not in a position
to help anyone at the moment.
VEHICLE REGISTRATION SEARCH
29H 2071
ISAAC CAR RENTALS
DONGDAEMUN-GU, SEOUL
DONGDAEMUN-GU
The person you have called
is not available.
You will be directed to voicemail
and charged after the beep.
MR. KIM
It looks like the car you're asking about
is currently being rented by a company.
A company? What's the name?
It says, "Sunshine Capital."
The address, please.
You're going to play a game now.
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Minus One.
I trust you know the rules.
You form a shape with each hand,
then take one away.
The game is decided
by the remaining hands.
Of course,
there's a penalty for the loser.
I'm sure you've seen this in movies.
It's called Russian Roulette.
I'll place one bullet into a revolver
and close it.
I'll point the gun at the loser's head
and pull the trigger.
Your odds of death are 1 in 6.
Your odds of survival are 5 in 6.
Not that bad, right?
All right. Now, let's play. On my count.
Rock, paper, scissors.
You didn't play.
You broke the rules for the first round.
Disqualified.
Now, let's play again.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Minus one.
Don't be so nervous.
Like I said,
your odds of survival are 5 in 6.
Let's play again.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Minus one.
It's getting a little boring, isn't it?
Let's reverse the odds now, shall we?
Your odds of survival are now 1 in 6.
Please don't…
Your odds of death are 5 in 6.
All right, let's play again.
Let's speed it up, okay?
Rock, paper, scissors. Minus one.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Minus one.
Too bad. You didn't take one away.
Disqualified.
Congratulations on your win.
Now, can we have a talk?
SUNSHINE CAPITAL
That's right.
The boss hasn't come back yet.
Seong says he and Woo-seok
were following that guy with the ddakji
when he lost contact with them.
How the hell would I know?
Anyway, gather everyone
and go to Daebang Station.
I'll pick up some weapons from the office.
Yeah.
I said Daebang Station, you idiot.
Not Sindaebang.
Don't make me
keep repeating myself, blockhead.
That's what I said! Call everyone now!
Goddamn idiot.
IOU
SEONG GI-HUN
CERTIFICATE OF BUSINESS REGISTRATION
PINK MOTEL
I found bloodstains there.
I'm sure they didn't get far
from that alley.
Check all the CCTV and dashcam footage
you can collect from the area
and keep asking around.
I'll join you soon.
It's been a long time, Mr. Seong Gi-hun.
You should've gotten
on that plane that day.
I changed my mind when I saw you.
It looks like
you've been trying hard to find me.
I wanted to thank you.
Thank me?
For inviting me to the game.
I won
and made it out with a fortune.
The decent thing to do
would be to thank you for it.
I'm just a messenger
who delivers invitations.
Who had you deliver those invitations?
Let me meet him. I have something to say.
Give me the message,
and I'll pass it along.
It's not something I can discuss
with an underling like you.
You prey on people
who are hanging by a thread
and con them at subway stations.
Someone like you wouldn't be able
to understand what I'm trying to say.
Mr. Seong.
How do you think I got to where I am now?
I don't care how you became their dog.
Bring me your master.
I used to work in the games
when I was younger.
I removed and burned the bodies
of countless people like you.
"These things aren't human."
"They're just trash,
utterly useless in this world."
I kept telling myself that
and worked hard for a few years.
Then they gave me a gun.
It felt pretty good.
Like my existence was acknowledged
for the first time in my life.
I don't know which year it was,
but one day,
I was about to shoot a man
who had lost a game.
The guy seemed familiar.
Guess who it was.
My dad.
My dad was suddenly
standing right in front of me.
He was in tears,
desperately begging me to spare his life.
I shot him right in the middle
of his forehead, and realized,
"Ah."
"I'm cut out for this job."
Whether you shoot people in there
or con them outside,
it doesn't change anything.
You have always been…
nothing more than their dog.
Mr. Seong.
Do you think you're special
because you won the game?
Someone like you
could never know…
or understand
how I made it out of there alive.
And how it feels…
to play the games.
Let's play a game.
I'm sure you've seen this in the movies.
It's called Russian Roulette.
Usually, you place one bullet in the gun,
spin the cylinder,
and pull the trigger.
And before the next round,
you spin the cylinder again.
It resets the odds back to 1 in 6.
But I'd like to make
this game a little more serious.
Because you're special, Mr. Seong.
Cut to the chase.
We'll take turns pulling the trigger
without spinning the cylinder again.
The bullet will be fired within
six attempts, and the game will be over.
What do you say?
I've always wondered
how you made it out of there alive.
For one thing,
you were even terrible at ddakji.
What's the matter?
Is your mind starting to race?
Now your odds of death are 1 in 2.
That's pretty high indeed.
I'm sure you're afraid.
Lots going through your mind.
Let me guess
what you're thinking right now.
"The gun is in my hand."
"Screw the rules.
Pull the trigger once or twice,
and I can blow this guy's face off."
Isn't that right?
If you want to meet the person
you mentioned earlier,
the key is in my pocket.
You can simply shoot me
with that gun and take it.
But I'll have you admit one thing.
That you're a piece of trash,
just like everyone else.
A piece of trash who got lucky
and made it out of the dumpster.
What's the matter?
Is your mind starting to race?
That's right.
Screw the rules.
Now, with a single pull of the trigger,
you could kill me.
But…
I'll have you admit one thing.
You put a mask over your face
and do whatever your master says.
You run, bark,
and wag your tail for them.
You're nothing more than their dog.
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song